Product

[Sales management Manage leads, deals, contacts, pipelines, access permissions & roles](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/sales-management.php)

[Contact center Omnichannel communications via CRM forms, website widget, live chat, WhatsApp, Instagram, telephony, email](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/contact-center.php)

[Sales team collaboration Work with chat, video calls, tasks, calendar, file storage, online documents](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/sales-team-collaboration.php)

[Sales enablement Get estimates, invoices, payments, catalog, inventory, e-signature, CRM store](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/sales-enablement.php)

[Analytics & reports Analyze sales funnel, employee performance, Sales Intelligence, BI Builder dashboards](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/analytics-and-reports.php)

[Mobile CRM Leads, deals, invoices, payments, telephony, emails, inventory, calendar at your fingertips](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/mobile-crm.php)

[Marketing Use email campaigns, social media ads, SMS, telemarketing, landing pages](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/marketing.php)

[Automation & integrations Set CRM rules and triggers, workflow automation, automated funnels, API](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/crm/automation-and-integrations.php)

[CoPilot in CRM Call audio-to-text transcription, call summary, field autocompletion in deals](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-crm)

[Task management Choose between Kanban board, Gantt chart, Scrum, task list](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/task-management.php)

[Task tracking Take advantage of checklists & sub-tasks, task summary, time tracking, focus & supervisor mode](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/task-tracking.php)

[API & integrations Connect your tasks to other services via API integration for advanced task automation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/api-and-integrations.php)

[Project management Use projects, workgroups, project planning, roles, access permissions](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/project-management.php)

[Employee performance Get productive with task reports, workload management, task efficiency & KPI](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/employee-performance.php)

[Mobile tasks Task creation, task tracking, notifications, comments, chat on the go](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/mobile-tasks.php)

[Project collaboration Work faster with chat, video calls, comments, file storage, documents, external users, task templates](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/project-collaboration.php)

[Automation Save time with automatic task creation and workflow automation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/tasks_and_projects/automation.php)

[CoPilot in Tasks AI-generated task descriptions, task summaries, checklists, comments](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-tasks)

[Online workspace Use chat, activity feed, comments, reactions, company-wide video announcements](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/communications/online-workspace.php)

[Online documents & file storage Store, share and edit documents online easily with co-workers using company drive](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/communications/online-documents-and-cloud-file-storage.php)

[Workgroups Create workgroups, invite external users, set access permissions and work on tasks and projects](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/communications/workgroups.php)

[Online meetings Do more with video calls, video conferencing, screen sharing, call recording and custom backgrounds](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/communications/online-meetings.php)

[Shared calendars Plan with company & personal calendar, open time slots, meeting room booking, calendar sync](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/communications/shared-calendars.php)

[Mobile communications Team messenger, video calls, comments, calendar, notifications anywhere](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/communications/mobile-communications.php)

[CoPilot in Chat Unlimited source of ideas, AI-generated texts, brainstorming, and more](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-chat)

[Website builder Use our free CMS, templates, hosting, AI-generated images and texts to create awesome sites](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/website-builder.php)

[Social selling Sell your products directly via Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp or Telegram](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/social-selling.php)

[Website forms Capture leads with custom order forms, registration & feedback forms, and forms with conditional fields](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/website-forms.php)

[Landing pages Generate leads with capture forms, automated funnels and Google Analytics integration](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/landing-pages.php)

[Online store Maximize ecommerce with inventory management, order processing, delivery and online payments](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/online-store.php)

[Mobile sites & online stores Responsive design, online orders, client management in your pocket](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/mobile-sites-and-stores.php)

[Website widget Enable widget to chat with site visitors, use popular messengers and accept callback requests](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/website-widget.php)

[Online marketing tools Increase sales with email marketing, Facebook or Google Ads, marketing automation, CRM integration](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/websites/marketing.php)

[CoPilot in Sites & Stores Compelling copy on demand, AI-generated images, detailed prompts, text translation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-sites-and-stores)

[Employee management Use employee profiles, company structure, access permissions, Active Directory](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/employee-management.php)

[Culture & engagement Get company news, polls, appreciation badges, tags, personal notifications](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/culture-and-engagement.php)

[Mobile HR Chat, video calls, employee profiles, approvals, notifications on the go](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/mobile-hr.php)

[Work management Track employee performance with KPI, work reports, supervisor view](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/work-management.php)

[Internal communications Communicate via video announcements, memos, public and private chats](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/internal-communications.php)

[CoPilot in Feed Thread summaries, AI-generated ideas, text editing & creation, AI-written responses, text translation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-feed)

[Information management Work with knowledge bases, online documents, file storage, access permissions](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/information-management.php)

[Automation Streamline operations with requests, approvals, expense reports, RPA, workflow automation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/hr_automation/automation.php)

[CoPilot in CRM Call audio-to-text transcription, call summary, field autocompletion in deals](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-crm)

[CoPilot in Tasks AI-generated task descriptions, task summaries, checklists, comments](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-tasks)

[CoPilot in Chat Unlimited source of ideas, AI-generated texts, brainstorming, and more](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-chat)

[CoPilot in Sites & Stores Compelling copy on demand, AI-generated images, detailed prompts, text translation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-sites-and-stores)

[CoPilot in Feed Thread summaries, AI-generated ideas, text editing & creation, AI-written responses, text translation](https://www.bitrix24.com/tools/copilot-ai-powered-tools-for-business.php#copilot-in-feed)

Resources

Learn

Connect

Read

Solutions

Role

Industry

Goal

Tool

Business size

Import & Export

Sales & CRM

Marketing

Tasks & Projects

Partners

For clients

For partners

Why bitrix24

Bitrix24 advantages

Our company

Latest from Bitrix24

[Demystifying AI: Understanding Its Impact in Today's Business World](https://www.bitrix24.com/articles/demystifying-ai-understanding-its-impact-in-today-s-business-world.php)

[How to Start a Project Like a Pro: A Beginner's Ultimate Guide](https://www.bitrix24.com/articles/how-to-start-a-project-like-a-pro-a-beginner-s-ultimate-guide.php)

Log In

Your Bitrix24

Authorize to enter  
your company's Bitrix24.

Enter[](https://www.bitrix24.net/qr/?user_lang=en)

Don't have Bitrix24 yet?

en

America

Europe

Asia

You can change your region here, if necessary

Privacy Policy
==============

Bitrix24 Privacy Policy
-----------------------

#### Contents:

[D. YOUR CHOICES, CHOICES FOR LIMITING THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA, RIGHTS AND PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS](#d)

[E. BITRIX24 INTEGRATIONS, THIRD PARTY LINKS AND EXTENSIONS PRIVACY STATEMENT](#e)

Last Updated: June 12, 2024

#### A. INTRODUCTION

This Website is operated by Bitrix24. The Data Controllers are Bitrix24 legal entities. Bitrix24 will have the meaning according to the Contracting Party section of Bitrix24 Terms of Service ([https://bitrix24.com/terms/](https://bitrix24.com/terms/)) depending on the domain zone registration of your customer account, the following legal entities will be your Data Controllers:  
a) Bitrix24 Ltd, a company registered under the laws of the Republic of Cyprus with its registered office at Frema House, office 102, No. 9, Constantinou Paparigopoulou Str., 3106, Limassol, Cyprus;  
b) Bitrix, Inc. a company organized under the laws of the Commonwealth of Virginia, United States of America with its registered address at 700 North Fairfax St., Suite 614-B, Alexandria, VA 22314, USA; and  
c) Bitrix24 India Private Limited with its registered office address is #66/1, Coles Road, C Stn F4, Benson Town, Bangalore, Bangalore North, Karnataka, India, 560046, and its affiliates (collectively, "Bitrix24", "We", "Us" "Our" or "Bitrix").  
Bitrix24 is committed to keeping your information secure and managing it in accordance with our legal responsibilities under the applicable privacy and data protection laws.

This Privacy Policy provides information about how we process personal information through the websites [www.bitrix24.eu](https://www.bitrix24.eu/), [www.bitrix24.com](https://www.bitrix24.com/), [www.bitrix24.de](https://www.bitrix24.de/), [www.bitrix24.pl](https://www.bitrix24.pl/), [www.bitrix24.it](https://www.bitrix24.it/), [www.bitrix24.com.tr](https://www.bitrix24.com.tr/), [www.bitrix24.com.br](https://www.bitrix24.com.br/), [www.bitrix24.es](https://www.bitrix24.es/), [www.bitrix24.fr](https://www.bitrix24.fr/), [www.bitrix24.cn](https://www.bitrix24.cn/), [www.bitrix24.cn/tc/](https://www.bitrix24.cn/tc/), [www.bitrix24.com/my/](https://www.bitrix24.com/my/), [www.bitrix24.com/th/](https://www.bitrix24.com/th), [www.bitrix24.in](https://www.bitrix24.in/), [www.bitrix24.co](https://www.bitrix24.co/), [www.bitrix24.mx](https://www.bitrix24.mx/), [www.bitrix24.uk](https://www.bitrix24.uk/), [www.bitrix24.id](https://www.bitrix24.id/), [www.bitrix24.vn](https://www.bitrix24.vn/), [www.bitrix24.jp](https://www.bitrix24.jp/), [mailinternetsub.com](https://mailinternetsub.com/) ("Website"), our mobile apps and our Products and Services.

Upon reading this Privacy Policy, you will be informed regarding the following:

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Website as well as through the Products and Services;  
2\. The organization collecting the information;  
3\. How the information is and will be used and disclosed;  
4\. With whom the information may be shared;  
5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information and your right;  
6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under Bitrix24's control; and  
7\. How you can access and correct any inaccuracies in the information collected about you.

BITRIX24 PRIVACY POLICY IS INCORPORATED AND MADE A PART OF BITRIX24 TERMS OF SERVICE ([WWW.BITRIX24.COM/TERMS/](https://www.bitrix24.com/terms/)). PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY. IT CONTAINS IMPORTANT INFORMATION THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW BEFORE CONTINUING TO USE OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES. BY CONTINUING TO USE BITRIX24'S WEBSITE AND SERVICES YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

Your use of the Bitrix24 website and the products and services provided herein, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") and Bitrix24's Terms of Service ([https://www.bitrix24.com/terms/](https://www.bitrix24.com/terms/)) and Bitrix24 Data Processing Agreement ([https://www.bitrix24.eu/upload/DPA/BitrixDPA.pdf](https://www.bitrix24.eu/upload/DPA/BitrixDPA.pdf)). By visiting the Bitrix24 Website or using any of its Products and Services (defined below), you agree to your personal information being used and disclosed in the manner set out in this Policy and in Bitrix24's Terms of Service.

You do not have to provide your personal information to us, but if you do not provide certain information it may affect the service we are able to provide to you.

By continuing to use this Website, you agree to us, as data controllers collecting and using your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and for the purposes of properly running the Site and offering our Products and Services to you.

#### Changes in the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically for changes. If you do not accept the amended Policy, please stop using this Website.

#### B. COLLECTED INFORMATION

#### Personally identifiable information We Collect

Most of the Products and Services offered to visitors of the Website require you to register for a user account with Bitrix24 ("User Account"). When registering for a User Account, Bitrix24 will ask you to voluntarily supply Bitrix24 with certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. Such information may include your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. The foregoing information is collected and processed by online payment services, including but not limited to merchant accounts services, which we may utilize for payment processing, including automatic subscription renewals. It is completely optional for you to register for a User Account or engage in activities requiring a User Account.

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:

* **Identity Data** includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, marital status, job title. In some cases we might request you to provide your identity documents.
* **Contact Data** includes billing address, email address and telephone numbers.
* **Transaction Data** includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us.
* **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
* **Profile Data** includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your preferences, feedback and survey responses.
* **Usage Data** includes information about how you use our website, products and services.
* **Marketing and Communications Data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

You never have to answer any questions, and you can decline this exchange of information at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some or all of the Products and Services. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as optional. If you do not provide the mandatory information with respect to a particular activity or purchase, you will not be able to engage in that activity or make such a purchase. Bitrix24 will inform you of the mandatory and/or optional character of the requested and/or required information.

You may be provided an opportunity to subscribe to a periodic newsletter and product updates. This newsletter allows Bitrix24 to inform you of new Products and Services, updates, as well as other news relevant to the company. The subscription service requires you to provide your first and last name, your email address, and other information. Optionally, you are asked to provide the name of the company you represent.

#### Browsing websites and mail client interactions

When you request a page from our Website or click an url link included in our email, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header, JavaScript or similar technical tools, including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information. We collect this information in order to make the Website function correctly and provide you the functionality that you see on the Website. We also use this information to better understand how visitors use the Website and how we can better adjust the Website, its contents, and functionality to meet the needs of our users.

#### Mobile Apps

When you download, access, and use the App, it may use technology to automatically collect:

Your Usage Details. When you access and use the App, we may automatically collect certain details of your access to and use of the App, including traffic data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on or through the App.

Device Information. We may collect information about your mobile device and internet connection, including the IP address, operating system, browser type, mobile network information, and the device's telephone number.

Stored Information and Files. The App also may access metadata and other information associated with other files stored on your device. This may include, for example, photographs, audio and video clips, personal contacts, and address book information.

Location Information. When You instruct Bitrix24 to collect your employees location and subject to their explicit consent this App may collect real-time information about the location of your device.

#### Files

Bitrix24 collects and stores the files you upload, download, or access via the Products and Services offered through the Website. We understand that these files may be confidential or contain sensitive information. Accordingly, Bitrix24 does not share or permit third parties to access such files. However, no password-protected system of data storage and retrieval can be made entirely impenetrable. Although Bixtrix24 uses a number of security technologies and procedures to make sure that the data on the Website is secure, it may be possible for an unauthorized third party to access, view, copy, modify and distribute the data and files you store on the Website or via Products and Services despite Bitrix24's efforts.

#### Your User Account and Public profile

As described above, you will be given an opportunity to create a User Account containing your personal information. A User Account is required for using most Products and Services offered on the Website.

#### Your public profile

Once the User Account is created, you may provide additional information to your profile, access, review and update your account information online via the Website.

Providing additional information about yourself beyond what is minimally required for the account creation is entirely up to you. Any information you provide at registration or in your profile section may be used by us as described in our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy. You can review the personal information you provide to us and make any desired changes to the information you publish at any time by logging in to your account on the Website.

If you wish to deactivate your User Account, you can do so through the User Account interface or by contacting Bitrix24 at [privacy@bitrix24.com](mailto:privacy@bitrix24.com). When you deactivate your User Account, all information stored and maintained as part of your account will be deleted from our servers, including the files you stored via the Website or its Products and Services.

#### Information Relating to Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16 without the consent of the child's holder of parental responsibility. You must be 16 years old or the age of majority in your jurisdiction in order to use our Website, Products or Services. If you are under 16 years old, you may only use our website with your parent or legal guardian's permission. Parents and Legal Guardians may request from us to review, delete or stop the collection of the personally identifiable information of their child by contacting us by letter (using the address information provided at the bottom of this page) or email to [privacy@bitrix24.com](mailto:privacy@bitrix24.com).

#### Securing the Transmission and Storage of Information

Bitrix24 is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information.

In particular, we use all reasonable endeavours to ensure that appropriate security measures are in place to protect your Personal Data. We apply the security measures foreseen in the applicable regulations as well as our own technical and organizational security measures including policy, governance, procedures, responsibilities, risk assessment; network and subprocessor security.

Bitrix24 operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. Bitrix24 takes steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and so we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Data transmitted through the Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

We treat the information you provide to us, including the Files, as confidential information; it is, accordingly, subject to our company's security procedures and corporate policies regarding protection and use of confidential information. After personally identifiable information reaches Bitrix24, it is stored on a server with physical and electronic security features as customary in the industry, including utilization of login/password procedures and electronic firewalls designed to block unauthorized access from outside of Bitrix24. Because laws applicable to personal information vary by country, our offices or other business operations may put in place additional measures that vary depending on the applicable legal requirements. Information collected on the sites covered by this Privacy Policy is processed and stored in the United States and possibly other jurisdictions and also in other countries where Bitrix24 and its service providers conduct business. All Bitrix24 employees are obligated by our privacy and security policies. Your information is only accessible to those employees who perform technical support of the service.

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always log out before leaving any site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users.

#### C. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

#### How Your Personal Information Is Used

On Contract Lawful basis

If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, such information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. We also use your personal information for registering you for an account or for a webinar, sending a confirmation e-mail, responding to your requests and helping to process the purchase or service you have selected, communicating with you when you contact a sales consultant or authorized partner, processing, fulfilling, and following up on transactions for our products and services, support, and training, to process any request by you for information or advice, to manage your account and content that you upload, to deal with enquiries, complaints and feedback from you and our partners;

Based on our Legitimate interests

Bitrix24 may use statistical data to help diagnose any problems with our server and administer the Website or to improve your browsing experience by personalising the Website;

We reserve the right to send a one-time registration confirmation email, and infrequent service alert messages to users to inform them of specific changes that may impact their ability to use a service they have previously signed up for, regardless of email contact opt-in status.

Based on our Legitimate interests and Your consent

We use your personal information to develop and conduct our business. Some examples of how we use personal information include: improving our products and services; personalizing communications with you; conducting customer surveys.

Bitrix24 collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select.

Based on your consent, your personal information also may be used to keep you informed about new products, product upgrades, patches, special offers, and other products and services of Bitrix24 and selected third parties if you have consented to receive such communications.

When you create a User Account with Bitrix24 and/or provide your e-mail address and other personal identification information, based on your personal preferences, we may periodically contact you via e-mail and provide information about special offers and promotions that may be of interest to you. These communications will relate to Bitrix24 offers and/or the promotions of select, reputable third parties with whom Bitrix24 has a strategic marketing relationship because they offer products or services that we believe would be of interest to you. We may use a third party e-mail service provider to send e-mails to you. This service provider is prohibited from using your e-mail address for any purpose other than to send Bitrix24 related e-mail. If you do not wish to receive e-mails with updates and information, please unsubscribe by sending email to: [unsubscribe@bitrix24.com](mailto:unsubscribe@bitrix24.com). In addition, every time you receive an e-mail you will be provided the choice to opt-out of future e-mails by following the instructions provided in the e-mail. You may also opt-out online by updating your User Account as described in the User Account section of this Privacy Policy (above).

Legal obligation

We may hold some of your information for complying with legal requirements and enforcing our website terms of use or otherwise protecting our legal rights.

We also reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding or if there has been a violation of any applicable licensing, warranty and purchase agreements.

Bitrix24 is retaining these rights because in limited cases we feel that we may need to contact you as a matter of law or regarding matters that will be important to you. These rights do not allow us to contact you to market a new or existing service if you have asked us not to do so, and issuance of these types of communications is rare.

#### Disclosure of your personal data to Third Parties

Bitrix24 uses services of third parties, such as e-mail service providers and hosting providers that act as independent contractors on behalf of Bitrix24. We will not share your information with any third parties for the purposes of direct marketing or any other purposes as Data Controller.

We have contracts in place with our data processors. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will not share your personal information with any organization apart from us. They will hold it securely and retain it for the period we instruct.

The data processing consisting in hosting provider services (storage and maintenance of databases containing your personal data, protected by password) is performed on our behalf and under written confidentiality agreements by our authorized data processor Amazon Web Services, (“AWS”), Frankfurt, Germany. As Amazon Web Services (“AWS”) is part of a global organization with local operating companies in a number of countries worldwide.

Bitrix24 will be liable for it's onward transfers of data to third parties.

Bitrix24 may disclose your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, a subpoena, or other legal process. Bitrix24 may also disclose personally identifiable information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating this Privacy Policy, the terms of your agreements with the Company (such as the Terms of Service) or to protect the safety of our users and the public or under confidentiality and licensing agreements with certain third parties which assist us in developing, operating and maintaining the Website and its content.

Bitrix24 may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to appropriate governmental authorities. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, Bitrix24 will provide this information upon receipt of appropriate documentation. Bitrix24 may also provide information to law enforcement to protect its property and the health and safety of individuals as permitted by statute.

Bitrix24 may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In the event that all or substantially all of Bitrix24's stock and/or all or substantially all assets are transferred or sold to another entity, Bitrix24 may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity. If, as a result of such a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a materially different manner, you will be given choice consistent with our policy regarding notification of changes.

#### Where we store your personal data

Data storage geography depending on Bitrix24 domain zone is described in the [Bitrix24 Infrastructure, Sub-processors and joint controllers section](https://www.bitrix24.com/upload/DPA/Bitrix24_Infrastructure_and_Sub.pdf).

Personal Data obtained via Bitrix24.eu, Bitrix24.de, Bitrix.it, Bitrix24.pl, Bitrix24.uk and Bitrix24.fr domain zones is processed by Alaio Cloud Limited registered on Republic of Cyprus inside the European Union Economic Area and stored inside the European Union in Frankfurt, Germany by Amazon Web Services data centers, which are fully GDPR compliant.

For more information about data processing activities related to Users registered through the domain names Bitrix24.com, Bitrix24.in, Bitrix24.tr, Bitrix24.cn, Bitrix24.mx, Bitrix24.co please consult [Bitrix24 Infrastructure, Sub-processors and joint controllers section](https://www.bitrix24.com/upload/DPA/Bitrix24_Infrastructure_and_Sub.pdf).

#### International transfers

Bitrix24 may process User Personal Data outside European Union area subject to appropriate safeguards under article 46 GDPR (specifically by the standard data protection clauses adopted by the European Commission in accordance with the examination procedure).

If your contracting party and Data Controller is Bitrix, Inc and you are in the EU, Switzerland or United Kingdom, the following will apply:  
a) Specific for data transfers from EU, UK and Switzerland to the USA, Bitrix24 complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Bitrix24 has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Bitrix24 has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). The Data Privacy Framework (DPF) list of participating organisations is available at [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/participant-search](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/participant-search). Under certain conditions, you can invoke the corresponding binding arbitration.  
The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Bitrix24 compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF) and the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF).  
b) Disputes resolution  
Bitrix24 Internal Complaints MechanismIn compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Bitrix24 commits to resolve DPF Principles-related complaints about our collection and use of your personal information. EU, UK and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF should first contact Bitrix24 at: privacy@bitrix24.com  
c) Alternative Dispute Resolution Body  
In compliance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF, Bitrix24 commits to refer unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal data received in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF and the Swiss-U.S. DPF to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider based in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your DPF Principles-related complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your DPF Principles-related complaint to your satisfaction, please visit [https://www.jamsadr.com/dpf-dispute-resolution](https://www.jamsadr.com/dpf-dispute-resolution) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

#### D. YOUR CHOICES, CHOICES FOR LIMITING THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA, RIGHTS AND PRIVACY-RELATED INQUIRIES AND COMPLAINTS

#### Choices Available to You

You can always choose whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information and that choice will not prevent you from using the Website. Please note, however, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information and you will be given an opportunity to "opt-in" and make your preference choices for any items that are optional and which are not prerequisite for our rendering such services.

You can choose at any time to opt out of receiving emails from Bitrix24 or from having your personally identifiable information shared with selected companies. If you wish to opt out, you can do so by editing your User Account preferences with respect to e-mail or the sharing of information. If you elect to "opt out" we will not, as applicable, share your personal information with third parties or send you emails. However, we may continue to use your personal information for internal purposes, to enhance your user experience or as necessary to administer the site or comply with applicable law.

#### California, Virginia, Colorado Privacy Choices

We will not share any Personal Data with third-parties for their direct marketing purposes to the extent prohibited by California, Virginia or Colorado law. If our practices change, we will do so in accordance with applicable laws and will notify you in advance.

#### Cookies and Tracking pixels (Device Data Collection Tools)

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

We use the following cookies:

* Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services.
* Analytical or performance cookies. These allow us to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.
* Functionality cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalise our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

Web beacons are very small images or small pieces of data embedded in images, also known as “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”, that can recognize Cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, a description of the page where the pixel tag is placed, and similar information from your computer or device.  
Some of Bitrix24 domains including bitrix24.com may use Device Data Collection Tools operated by third parties, including TikTok, to collect information about how users use your websites.

Choices About cookie usage

You can opt out from any not strictly necessary cookie installation on your first visit of our web sites.

Additionally, you can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

You may setup your privacy preferences at your [Facebook account privacy settings](https://www.facebook.com/help/193677450678703).

You can opt-out of having your site activity available to Google Analytics by installing the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en#:~:text=You%20can%20opt%2Dout%20of,Google%20Analytics%20about%20visit%20activity.):

You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so may adversely affect your ability to perform certain transactions, use certain functionality and access certain content on our Website.

#### E. BITRIX24 INTEGRATIONS, THIRD PARTY LINKS AND EXTENSIONS PRIVACY STATEMENT

**Introduction**. This Privacy Statement describes how the Personal Data is processed under Bitrix24 Third Party integrations, Third Party links and Non-Bitrix Applications.  
**Definitions**

“Bitrix24,” “we,” “us” “our” means Alaio Inc. and its affiliates;  
“Customer”, “You” means the organization that subscribes to the Services and through whom you, the end user of such Services, are provided access to the Bitrix24 Services;  
“Customer Data” means electronic data and information submitted by or for Customer to the Services;  
“Personal data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person;  
“Services” means products and services that are ordered by our Customers and made available online by Bitrix24 as described in [Bitrix24's Terms of Service](https://www.bitrix24.com/terms/);  
“Third Party Services” means services that are provided to the Customer by a third party and/or listed on an online directory, catalog or marketplace of applications that interoperate with Bitrix24 Services (“Non-Bitrix Applications”).

**Limited Use disclosure**

Bitrix24 use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.

**What data is collected?**

**Google Services Integrations**

If you connect your Bitrix24 account to apps or services provided by other parties, such as Google, certain Customer Data may be collected from your device by Google. This data may be collected automatically through the use of application programming interfaces such as the Google API Services or Gmail's API (OAuth), and may include:

* The contents, metadata and related information of emails, Google calendar events and stored files when you choose to sync your App with Gmail, calendar and cloud storage services (Google Drive);
* Email addresses of your Inbox and Sent folders, when you choose to sync your Bitrix24 account and Gmail with your device's address book; and
* Customer Data that you send from your Bitrix24 account to Google, or data that you request from any of the Google services, automatically or otherwise. Note that, as a security precaution, if you choose to connect your Bitrix24 account to apps or services provided by Google and you request data from any of the Google services, information that identifies you or your device may also be sent in order to authenticate the request. You can revoke access at any time.
* App's use of information received, and App's transfer of information to any other app, from Google APIs will adhere to [Google's Limited Use Requirements](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional-requirements-for-specific-api-scopes).
* App's use of information received from Gmail APIs will adhere to [Google's Limited Use Requirements](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional-requirements-for-specific-api-scopes).

**Bitrix24 Two-way synchronization:**

* Two-way synchronization between Bitrix24 and Gmail means that even if you work with emails in Gmail, you'll have copies of those in Bitrix24 CRM or Webmail. Also, you can send emails directly from inside Bitrix24 using Gmail when this integration is enabled. If you'd like more information about this integration, please see [https://helpdesk.bitrix24.com/open/8236675/](https://helpdesk.bitrix24.com/open/8236675/);
* Calendar Two-way synchronization between Bitrix24 and Google Calendars means all events created in Google Calendar are automatically synched with Bitrix24 calendars and vice-versa. If you'd like more information about this integration, please see [https://helpdesk.bitrix24.com/open/12506218/](https://helpdesk.bitrix24.com/open/12506218/);
* Google Docs: Google Docs can be used inside Bitrix24 account for viewing and editing documents online. If you'd like more information about this integration, please see [https://helpdesk.bitrix24.com/open/2154445/](https://helpdesk.bitrix24.com/open/2154445/)

In certain countries, for example on the bitrix24.com related websites, Third parties such as Microsoft may collect or receive Personal Data from individuals visiting Our websites in accordance with its privacy policy: [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement). To access and control this data collection please visit Microsoft opt out page: [https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings/signedout](https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings/signedout)

**How Your Personal Information Is Used via the Third party integrations:**

Based on our legitimate interests or as necessary to perform our contract with you, to administer, improve and provide to you our extended integration Services upon your request.

Legal obligation  
We may hold or request some of your information for complying with legal requirements and enforcing our website terms of use or otherwise protecting our legal rights.

In order to comply with the United States and European Union export controls and economic sanctions laws and regulations, including but not limited to, the United States Export Administration Regulations (“EAR”), regulations promulgated by the US Department of the Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (“OFAC”), and regulations promulgated by the Council of the European Union (“EU”), in certain cases Bitrix24 might request you to provide your identity documentation.

We also reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding or if there has been a violation of any applicable licensing, warranty and purchase agreements.

Bitrix24 is retaining these rights because in limited cases we feel that we may need to contact you as a matter of law or regarding matters that will be important to you. These rights do not allow us to contact you to market a new or existing service if you have asked us not to do so, and issuance of these types of communications is rare.

**Disclosure of your personal data to Third Parties**

Bitrix24 is not responsible for the data processing practices of any Third Party Providers. We encourage you to review your Third Party Providers' respective privacy notices before enabling a Third Party Service integration.

**Choices Available to You**

You can always choose whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information and that choice will not prevent you from using our Services. Please note, however, if you should choose not to make available some of your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services described in this Integrations, Third Party links and extensions privacy statement.

#### F. DATA RETENTION

Bitrix24 may retain your Personal Data for a period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection (see the section “4. How Your Personal Information Is Used via the Third party integrations”).

#### G. YOUR RIGHTS

In European Union, UK, Switzerland and some other jurisdictions you may have the following rights concerning our processing of your personal data:

Right to access. You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal information. This right always applies;

Right to rectification. You have the right to ask us to rectify information you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete. This right always applies;

Right to erasure. This right is applicable when one of the following applies:

(a) the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed;  
(b) the data subject withdraws consent on which the processing is based or where there is no other legal ground for the processing;  
(c) the data subject objects to the processing and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing;  
(d) the personal data have been unlawfully processed;

Right to restriction of processing. When processing is restricted, we will store your personal data, but not further process it;

Right to data portability. Is your right to receive the personal data which you have given to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and the right to transmit that data to another controller from the current controller applicable if: The processing is based on consent or on a contract, and the processing is carried out by automated means;

Right to object. You have the right to object to processing (on grounds relating your particular situation) if we process your information in our legitimate interests. The only reasons we will be able to deny your request is if we can show compelling legitimate grounds for the processing, which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of a legal claims or if the processing of data is necessary for the performance of our contract with you;

Right to withdraw your consent at any time in case of any consent-based processing of your personal data without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before your withdrawal; and

Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

You may exercise your legal rights by contacting us via email to [privacy@bitrix24.com](mailto:privacy@bitrix24.com). This request must include at least the following information: the link to your portal and your administrator registration email address.

Bitrix24 takes and addresses its users' privacy concerns with utmost respect and attention. If you believe that there was an instance of non-compliance with this Privacy Policy with regard to your personal information or you have other related inquiries or concerns, you may write or contact Bitrix24 at email: [privacy@bitrix24.com](mailto:privacy@bitrix24.com).

In your message, please describe in as much detail as possible the nature of your inquiry or the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your inquiry or complaint promptly.

Please note that if you provide Bitrix24 with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), Bitrix24 cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored.

You may exercise your legal rights by contacting our Data Protection and Grievance Officer Elena Riazanova via email to [privacy@bitrix24.com](mailto:privacy@bitrix24.com).

Bitrix24

Support

Resources

On-premise

Compare to

Apps

Partners

* Privacy

© 2024 Alaio

Privacy Overview

**Cookies:** This website uses cookies for analytical and technical reasons. ‘Analytical Cookies’ are inserted by Google Analytics to help us understand which countries our visitors come from, which pages they visit and what actions they take on this site. ‘Strictly Necessary Cookies’, as the name implies, are a type of cookies that are required for proper functioning of certain features of this website, such as the ability to use live chat. Disabling these cookies will disable access to those features and degrade your website experience.

Cookies of both types can be enabled or disabled within this plugin.

Cookie Settings

 Strictly Necessary Cookies

 Do Not Sell or Share My Information

Cookie Policy

More information about our [Cookie Policy](https://www.bitrix24.com/privacy/#d3)

We use cookies to enhance your browsing experience - [Find out more](https://www.bitrix24.com/about/cookie-policy/). By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Change your [cookie settings](#).

Got it
